http://www.standoffsystems.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Gyford Standoff Systems
LoginRegister
775.829.7272
info@standoffsystems.com
MenuShopStandOffsCapsEdge GripsBarrelsLED StandOffsHingesHubs CloseKitsAluminum StandOff KitsStainless Steel StandOff KitsEdge Grips KitsPanel Clip KitsWS Wire KitsWL Wire KitsEZ Wire KitsStructureLite Kits CloseWireWireLiteWire SuspensionEZ CloseRodsEZ CloseSurface Mounted GrippersNon-AdjustableAdjustableReplacement Parts CloseStructureLiteExtrusionExtrusion InsertsExtrusion CapsExtrusion ConnectorsBall TravelersHingesPlates and FeetReplacement Parts CloseHardwareThreaded Studs, Rods & Set ScrewsAnchorsScrewsAssembly Set ScrewsOther CloseToolsDrill Bits & DriversWrenches & TightenersWire Cutters & CrimpersInsert BitsRod Drilling Jig & Roll Pin CloseCustom Colors, Finishes & Designs CloseCustom Shop CloseShop All Products Close CloseGalleryHow-To GuidesResourcesBlogSubmit Your PhotosPrintable How-to GuidesFAQsProduct CatalogFind an Authorized RetailerBecome an Authorized Retailer CloseAbout UsCareers CloseContact UsLogin
Search for:
MenuShopStandOffsCapsEdge GripsBarrelsLED StandOffsHingesHubs CloseKitsAluminum StandOff KitsStainless Steel StandOff KitsEdge Grips KitsPanel Clip KitsWS Wire KitsWL Wire KitsEZ Wire KitsStructureLite Kits CloseWireWireLiteWire SuspensionEZ CloseRodsEZ CloseSurface Mounted GrippersNon-AdjustableAdjustableReplacement Parts CloseStructureLiteExtrusionExtrusion InsertsExtrusion CapsExtrusion ConnectorsBall TravelersHingesPlates and FeetReplacement Parts CloseHardwareThreaded Studs, Rods & Set ScrewsAnchorsScrewsAssembly Set ScrewsOther CloseToolsDrill Bits & DriversWrenches & TightenersWire Cutters & CrimpersInsert BitsRod Drilling Jig & Roll Pin CloseCustom Colors, Finishes & Designs CloseCustom Shop CloseShop All Products Close CloseGalleryHow-To GuidesResourcesBlogSubmit Your PhotosPrintable How-to GuidesFAQsProduct CatalogFind an Authorized RetailerBecome an Authorized Retailer CloseAbout UsCareers CloseContact UsLogin
Search for:
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Gyford Productions, LLC
Table of Contents
Information We Collect
How We Use Your Information
How We Share Your Information
Opt Out of Gyford Remarketing
Information We Collect
Our Service: We may collect personally identifiable information about you through our website when you register for an account. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information also. We also collect data through our partners (customers) to analyze usage of their websites. When you use our website or if you visit such websites, your browser may send us certain information about you as described below. We may send you service-related emails related to your account or promotional emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them.
Cookies Information: We may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us learn about your behavior and usage patterns when you are on our website. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We use cookies to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our website; (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (c) diagnose or fix technology problems; and (d) allow us to deliver advertisements to you as described below.
Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page on our Service. When you access the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.
Clear Gifs Information: When you access the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your account is collected using these clear gifs. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our Service, and make our website better for our users.
These technologies mentioned above do not collect personal information about you and only collect data in the aggregate.
How We Use Your Information
We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our website. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our website; (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (c) diagnose or fix technology problems; and (d) allow our partners to deliver advertisements to you as described below.
How We Share Your Information
Personally Identifiable Information: Gyford will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We will not store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Gyford. Any personally identifiable information you elect to make publically available on the website, such as posting comments on our blog page, will be available to other users. If you remove information that you have made public on the website, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the website, or if other users have copied or saved that information. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at info@standoffsystems.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We have the option to publish A/B testing results for the website. Such results consist solely of non-personally identifiable information. If you choose to publish such results on our website, you understand and agree that this information, along with any personally identifiable information you choose to make available in connection with such results, will be made publically available. By publishing your results on the Gyford website, you agree that you have obtained all necessary consents to make such information public and that doing so will not violate any laws. If you remove information that you have made public on the website, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other users have copied or saved that information. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.
Instances where we are required to share your information: Gyford will disclose your information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our website; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Gyford, our users or others.
Ads: We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. In connection with this advertising, we, along with third-party business partners, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to allow our third-party business partners, including Google, ad servers, and ad networks, to serve you advertisements (“ads”) based on your prior visits to our Service. These ads are delivered to you on third-party websites and services across the Internet. These third-party business partners use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on third-party sites, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. Along with cookies, they may also use other technologies (such as JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns on the website, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to optimize and personalize the advertising content. Gyford does not sell, rent, or share the information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party business partners for such parties’ own marketing purposes. You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.
Opt out of Gyford remarketing
Gyford’s remarketing opt-out tool uses cookies and will only opt out the specific computer you are on.
The Gyford Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party ad servers and ad networks. Please contact or consult the respective privacy policies of such ad servers or ad networks for more information.
Storage and Processing
Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Gyford or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Gyford or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
How We Protect Your Information
Gyford is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Gyford or guarantee that your information on the website may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@standoffsystems.com.
Compromise of Personal Information
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Gyford will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.
Choices About Your Information
You can review, correct, update or delete inaccuracies to the information about you that Gyford keeps on file by logging into your account to update your password and billing information. Alternately, you can contact us directly at info@standoffsystems.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Notification Procedures
It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the website, as determined by Gyford in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
If we change our privacy policies and procedures materially, we will post those changes on the website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective and update the ‘effective date’ at the top of this page.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at info@standoffsystems.com, or send mail to:
Gyford Productions, LLC
891 Trademark Dr
Reno, NV 89521
775.829.7272
SIGN UP FOR GYFORD ENEWS
CONTACT A SPECIALIST
REQUEST A CATALOG
Products
Aluminum StandOff KitsStainless Steel StandOff KitsEdge Grips KitsPanel Clip KitsWS Wire KitsWL Wire KitsEZ Wire KitsStructureLite Kits Back
ExtrusionExtrusion InsertsExtrusion CapsExtrusion ConnectorsBall TravelersHingesPlates and FeetReplacement Parts Back
Hardware
Threaded Studs, Rods & Set ScrewsAnchorsScrewsAssembly Set ScrewsOther Back
Tools
Drill Bits & DriversWrenches & TightenersWire Cutters & CrimpersInsert BitsRod Drilling Jig & Roll Pin Back
BlogSubmit Your PhotosPrintable How-to GuidesFAQsProduct CatalogFind an Authorized RetailerBecome an Authorized Retailer Back
About Us
Careers Back
Contact UsLogin
test
My AccountCheckoutCartShopUpdate UserRegisterWelcome To Gyford
